playsearchnow.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy

**_Play.Search.Now - Privacy Policy_**

Last Update: May 28, 2018

**Privacy Notice  **

This Privacy Policy is part of the Play.Search.Now (the “Company,” “we,” or “us”) End User License Agreement available at End User License Agreement, and applies to all users of the Play.Search.Now browser search extension (the “Extension”) and this website (the “Website”), together with any updates or upgrades that may become available. we refer to our Extension, Website , online services, and apps as "Services").

This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of our Services and govern your access to and use of Software. The Product is directed for use by adults.

**This Privacy Notice And Your Acceptance**

Please read our Privacy Policy carefully before using or accessing the Services or any portion of them. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy do not install or use the Extension or this Website. You may disable or uninstall the Extension at any time by following the instructions provided in the End User License Agreement.

** Type Of Information and  Data We Collect**

_Personal Information_ : means information about you that specifically identifies you or, when combined with other information, can be used to identify you. We do not collect any personal information that can identify you.

_Non-Personal Information_ : means information that alone cannot identify you, including data received and/or extract from your device upon operation of the Extension.

When operating the Extension and executing the Services we collect non personal information of end users that includes the following: operating system type and version, installed browsers type and versions language, access timestamp browsing data and search queries. At all time, we make sure to extract and store the data in an anonymous and aggregative manner.

We also collect the device IP address that is allocated by the Internet service provider only for purpose of extracting the country and language. We do not keep the IP. In some jurisdictions and given specific circumstances, IP address may be considered to be personal information when used with other information in an attempt to individually identify users. However, we make no such use in the data we collect, and we make no attempt or effort to personally identify any user.

**How Collected Information Is Used and Disclosed**

The information collected is used for the purpose of providing you with search results customized to your preferences as typed by you, and to extract statistics and aggregated data, therefore increase our ability to facilitate customized results.

Likewise, when you use the Extension to click on services that are streaming certain content, submit search terms, or otherwise engage with Third Party Content, the Extension automatically send your search query or the term you clicked on, to our partners’ servers in order to return the requested information to you.

**Cookies**.

 A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your browser storage. The Website may use cookies, however, the cookie is not used as a data tracking technology, neither it is used to  identify you or to collect personally identifiable information about you.

**Changing your cookie settings:** You may choose to set Your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, note that some parts of the Website may not function properly.

**Third Party Content**

The Extension and Website may integrate third party content (“Third Party Content”) in order to display search results to you. Such Third Party Content may include feeds, search results, APIs, links, information, websites, web pages, services, claims, promotions, offers, statements, data files, images, graphics, software, videos, music, photographs, sounds, links to third party websites that are controlled and maintained by others, other content displayed, promoted, or otherwise made available through third parties.

Such Third Party Content may also include advertising, or advertising-supported search results, which will be displayed to you if you use the search box or click on services that are streaming certain content.

Third Party Content providers may also use cookies.

**Disclaimers**

Third Party Content and Data Collection. Please be notified that in this Privacy Policy, the definition of Services does not include any Third Party Content or Third Party use of tracking technologies. these are governed respectively by the third party’s privacy policy (available at the links referred to _below_ ) and its End user License Agreement.

The Company does not control any Third Party Content that may be displayed to you when you use the Extension or Website. We are neither affiliated with nor responsible for the privacy practices of any partners or third parties who advertise or link to any websites, products, services or offers through the Extension or Website, or who otherwise provide Third Party Content. Once you view or click on a search result, streaming provider, advertisement or link, you should carefully review the applicable privacy policy of such third party service or site. Even if a third party is affiliated with us, we do not control its content, its websites or its tracking practices, each of which may have a separate privacy policy. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of each site you visit.

**Uninstalling The Extension.  **You may disable or uninstall the Extension at any time by following the instructions provided in the End User License Agreement.

**Modifications to This Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to revise or update this Privacy Notice at any time. The last revision will be reflected in the "Last Updated" heading. Your continued use of the Extension means you consent to such changes and your agreement to be bound by them. Please make sure to review our Privacy Notice periodically. If you do not agree to any modification, you must uninstall the Extension.

**How to Contact the Company**

If you have any questions or wish to contact us about this Privacy Policy, please email [support@playsearchnow.com](mailto:support@playsearchnow.com)

**_Links to Third Party service providers’ privacy policy and opt-out option_**
